Tufts New England Medical Center Planning Office Records UA014
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Subject files, 1932 -- 1980; 1960 -- 1971; UA014.006; 13.2 Linear Feet
  - Misc. Housing Studies, 1961 -- 1972; UA014.006.006.00007 (Box 6)
  - Misc. Decentralization: The Potential for Change- B. Willis, 1961 -- 1972; UA014.006.006.00008 (Box 6)
  - MEB: Preliminary program (original copy), 1969; UA014.006.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - Main Dental Clinic Records; Planning Office T-NEMC, UA014.006.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - Makaren Thesis Pediatic nursing, 1961; UA014.006.006.00011 (Box 6)
  - Married Student Housing, 1964; UA014.006.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - Haster Programme and Programming Date, 1961; UA014.006.006.00013 (Box 6)
  - Master Planning, 1962 -- 1971; UA014.006.006.00014 (Box 6)
  - Medical Education Building Cost-Benefit Analysis, 1970; UA014.006.006.00015 (Box 6)
  - Medical Education Building: Reused Program, 1970; UA014.006.006.00016 (Box 6)
  - Memorand- H.Bogen, Architect (1959), 1970; UA014.006.006.00017 (Box 6)
  - Mental Health I- H. Field, 1962 -- 1967; UA014.006.006.00018 (Box 6)
  - Mental Health Book I, 1964 -- 1968; UA014.006.006.00019 (Box 6)
  - Mental Health Book III, 1967 -- 1969; UA014.006.006.00020 (Box 6)
  - Mental Health Catchment Area Demographic Data, 1966; UA014.006.006.00021 (Box 6)
  - Mental Health Grant Account, 1965 -- 1968; UA014.006.006.00022 (Box 6)
  - NEMC Hopsitlas Adminstrative "On-Call" Book, 1969; UA014.006.007.00001 (Box 7)
  - Notes, 1965 -- 1970; UA014.006.007.00002 (Box 7)
  - Nurses Study, Misc. Hospital Study Information, 1963 -- 1968; UA014.006.007.00003 (Box 7)
  - O.P.D. Diagrams, UA014.006.007.00004 (Box 7)
  - Office Memo: Elliot P. Rothman, 1963 -- 1964; UA014.006.007.00005 (Box 7)
  - Office Organization, 1956 -- 1968; UA014.006.007.00007 (Box 7)
  - Office Staff, 1969; UA014.006.007.00008 (Box 7)
  - Office Trips General, 1960 -- 1966; UA014.006.007.00009 (Box 7)
  - Office Visitors, 1965 -- 1969; UA014.006.007.00010 (Box 7)
  - Organization and Faculty - School of Dental Medicine, UA014.006.007.00011 (Box 7)
  - Organization and Program of T-N.E. Medical Center - Confidential, 1958; UA014.006.007.00012 (Box 7)
  - P.I.1.2. NEMCH Progress, 1966; UA014.006.007.00013 (Box 7)
  - Pathology, 1967; UA014.006.007.00014 (Box 7)
  - Pedestrian Traffic Survey & Childhood Accidents, 1962 -- 1963; UA014.006.007.00015 (Box 7)
  - People-Work Equipment Survey, 1963 -- 1964; UA014.006.007.00016 (Box 7)
  - Personnel Charts, Appendix, 1964; UA014.006.007.00017 (Box 7)
  - Planning Guide for N.E. Center Hospital, 1965; UA014.006.007.00018 (Box 7)
  - Planning Guide, Section II, 1966; UA014.006.007.00019 (Box 7)
  - Post Construction Site Visit of NEMC Hospitals and T-NEM Schools, 1973; UA014.006.007.00020 (Box 7)
  - Pratt Clinic: New England Hospital Annual Reports, UA014.006.007.00021 (Box 7)
  - Preliminary Analysis of Educational Facilities, UA014.006.007.00022 (Box 7)
  - Preliminary Analysis of Educational Facilities, UA014.006.007.00023 (Box 7)
  - Preliminary Circulation Analysis - Confidential Report, 1961; UA014.006.007.00024 (Box 7)
  - Preliminary Survey of Program and Space Needs, 1962; UA014.006.007.00025 (Box 7)
  - Program Material for West Broadway Community Multiservice Center, 1969; UA014.006.007.00026 (Box 7)
  - Programming Manual - New Design Project, Boston Floating Hospital, Copy Hermann H. Field, 1963 -- 1974; UA014.006.007.00027 (Box 7)
  - Project W-235: New Design Concept - Childrens' Hospital, 1962 -- 1966; UA014.006.007.00028 (Box 7)
  - Project Reports, 1965; UA014.006.007.00029 (Box 7)
  - Property Adjustment & Development Needs, 1963 -- 1965; UA014.006.007.00030 (Box 7)
  - Property Adjustment & Development Needs, 1964; UA014.006.007.00031 (Box 7)
  - Proposals - NEMC, 1968 -- 1969; UA014.006.007.00032 (Box 7)
  - Proposals for a Dental Center, 1960; UA014.006.007.00033 (Box 7)
  - Proposals for a Dental Center - Tufts University, 1960; UA014.006.007.00034 (Box 7)
  - Proposal for Parking Facilities Construction, 1969; UA014.006.007.00035 (Box 7)
  - Psychiatric Out-Patient Service, Patient Population Statistics, 1966; UA014.006.007.00036 (Box 7)
  - Public Facilities Department, 1969 -- 1970; UA014.006.007.00037 (Box 7)
  - Public Relations, 1963 -- 1967; UA014.006.007.00038 (Box 7)
  - Purchase Order, "Evaluation of Hospital Design: A Holistic Approach," H.H. Field, 1975; UA014.006.007.00039 (Box 7)
  - Q.S.C.C. - Common Bond, 1970; UA014.006.008.00001 (Box 8)
  - Q.S.C.C. - History, Dr. Sussman, 1969; UA014.006.008.00002 (Box 8)
  - Q.S.C.C. - Common Bond, 1968 -- 1969; UA014.006.008.00003 (Box 8)
  - Q.S.C.C. - Organization, 1968 -- 1971; UA014.006.008.00004 (Box 8)
  - Quincy School, 1967 -- 1978; UA014.006.008.00005 (Box 8)
  - Quincy School: $39,000 Planning Grant, 1967; UA014.006.008.00006 (Box 8)
  - Quincy School: Arch. Comm., 1970 -- 1971; UA014.006.008.00007 (Box 8)
  - Quincy School: Book I, 1966 -- 1967; UA014.006.008.00008 (Box 8)
  - Quincy School: Book II, 1967 -- 1968; UA014.006.008.00009 (Box 8)
  - Quincy School: Book III, 1967 -- 1968; UA014.006.008.00010 (Box 8)
  - Quincy School: Book IV, 1968 -- 1969; UA014.006.008.00011 (Box 8)
  - Quincy School Community Council, 1969 -- 1977; UA014.006.008.00012 (Box 8)
  - Quincy School: Design Requirements, 1970; UA014.006.008.00013 (Box 8)
  - Quincy School: Filing & Document Orders, 1970; UA014.006.008.00014 (Box 8)
  - Quincy School: "General Correspondence, 1964", 1964 -- 1965; UA014.006.008.00015 (Box 8)
  - Quincy School: Handicapped, 1970; UA014.006.008.00016 (Box 8)
  - Quincy School: Health Project, 1969 -- 1970; UA014.006.008.00017 (Box 8)
  - Quincy School: Housing, 1969 -- 1971; UA014.006.008.00018 (Box 8)
  - Quincy School: Joint Use Design Study, 1970 -- 1971; UA014.006.008.00019 (Box 8)
  - Quincy School: Medical Psychiatric Program for Quincy School, 1966; UA014.006.008.00020 (Box 8)
  - Quincy School: Meetings, 1966 -- 1970; UA014.006.008.00021 (Box 8)
  - Quincy School: Memo on Handicapped, 1970; UA014.006.008.00022 (Box 8)
  - Quincy School: Memos, 1969 -- 1972; UA014.006.008.00023 (Box 8)
  - Quincy School Planning: Grant, 1968 -- 1969; UA014.006.009.00001 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Planning Project: Title III ESEA, Monthly Reports, 1967; UA014.006.009.00002 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School: Program Requirements and Design Specifications, 1969; UA014.006.009.00003 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Second Stage Planning, 1969; UA014.006.009.00004 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Advisory Council, 1970; UA014.006.009.00005 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Advisory Council Meetings, 1969; UA014.006.009.00006 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Advisory Council Minutes, 1969; UA014.006.009.00007 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project, 1978; UA014.006.009.00008 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Architect's Committee, 1970; UA014.006.009.00009 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Beacon St. & E.P.C., 1970; UA014.006.009.00010 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Board Meetings, 1971; UA014.006.009.00011 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Carbon Minutes of Meetings, 1966 -- 1967; UA014.006.009.00012 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Comprehensive Health Care - Castle Square, Minutes, 1967; UA014.006.009.00013 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Funding Grants, Correspondence, 1968 -- 1975; UA014.006.009.00014 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: General Planning, 1967; UA014.006.009.00015 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Health Care Grant, Year 1 & 2, 1968; UA014.006.009.00016 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Health Project Terminal Report, 1970; UA014.006.009.00017 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Health Services for the Chinese Community, Memorandum - S.S. Gellis MD, 1967; UA014.006.009.00018 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Miscellaneous Clipplings on the Quincy School Project, 1966 -- 1967; UA014.006.009.00019 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Monthly Reports, 1966 -- 1967; UA014.006.009.00020 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: On-Going Health, 1968 -- 1970; UA014.006.009.00021 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Operational Grant, Original Copy, 1966; UA014.006.009.00022 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Original, "A School in the City", 1969; UA014.006.009.00023 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Outline of Year II of Planning for Quincy School (Memorandum - H. Forsell), UA014.006.009.00024 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Parks and Recreation Department, 1970; UA014.006.009.00025 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Photos - Old Quincy School, UA014.006.009.00026 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Proposals - Pilot, Health Grant, Annual Reports, 1968; UA014.006.009.00027 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Plan In, Press Kit, Remarks, Coverage, 1970; UA014.006.009.00028 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Planning and Advisory Councils, Working Committee, 1968 -- 1969; UA014.006.009.00029 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Press, 1970; UA014.006.009.00030 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Press Coverage, 1969 -- 1970; UA014.006.009.00031 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Press Coverage, 1969; UA014.006.009.00032 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Program Approval, 1970; UA014.006.009.00033 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Proposal Priorities, 1971; UA014.006.009.00034 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Publicity Material, 1970; UA014.006.009.00035 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Quincy School Total Health, Final Report, 1967 -- 1970; UA014.006.009.00036 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Report and Media Articles, 1967 -- 1970; UA014.006.009.00037 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Status Report, 1970; UA014.006.009.00038 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Status Report, 1970; UA014.006.009.00039 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Status Report, Revised, 1970; UA014.006.009.00040 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Thesis - Jim Meier, 1970; UA014.006.009.00041 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Working Committee, 1970; UA014.006.009.00042 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School Project: Working Committee Meeting, 1970; UA014.006.009.00043 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School: School Department, 1970; UA014.006.009.00044 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School, Special Education: The Integration of Idiosyncratic Children into the Prospective Quincy School - Hays, B., 1967; UA014.006.009.00045 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School: Surveys, 1970; UA014.006.009.00046 (Box 9)
  - Quincy School: TNEMC Reports, 1970 -- 1971; UA014.006.009.00047 (Box 9)
  - Recreation, 1967 -- 1970; UA014.006.010.00001 (Box 10)
  - A Regional Medical Education Program: Progress Report, 1973; UA014.006.010.00002 (Box 10)
  - Renovations - Tufts, 1970; UA014.006.010.00003 (Box 10)
  - Report of Director of Planning, 1962 -- 1968; UA014.006.010.00004 (Box 10)
  - Report on Social and Economic Implications of TNEMC Development Plan, 1962; UA014.006.010.00005 (Box 10)
  - A Report to Temple University on Its Health Sciences Center, 1969; UA014.006.010.00006 (Box 10)
  - Research report 1, 1963; UA014.006.010.00007 (Box 10)
  - Research report 2, Boston Floating Hospital, 1963; UA014.006.010.00008 (Box 10)
  - Research report 3, Boston Floating Hospital, 1965; UA014.006.010.00009 (Box 10)
  - Research reports drafts, Michael Sokoloff, 1963; UA014.006.010.00010 (Box 10)
  - Rothman, Eliot, Planning Office, 1964; UA014.006.010.00011 (Box 10)
  - Sheltered housing, 1971; UA014.006.010.00012 (Box 10)
  - Site plan diagrams, 1980; UA014.006.010.00013 (Box 10)
  - Solomon, Paul, M.D., Visiting staff - BFH, 1962; UA014.006.010.00014 (Box 10)
  - South Cove photos, UA014.006.010.00015 (Box 10)
  - South Cove agencies, 1970; UA014.006.010.00016 (Box 10)
  - South Cove general, 1965 -- 1969; UA014.006.010.00017 (Box 10)
  - South Cove Project, 1962 -- 1968; UA014.006.010.00018 (Box 10)
  - South Cove Project memorandum, 1964; UA014.006.010.00019 (Box 10)
  - South Cove Project, miscellaneous information on South Cove urban renewal plan, 1965; UA014.006.010.00020 (Box 10)
  - South Cove Project, population study, 1965 -- 1975; UA014.006.010.00021 (Box 10)
  - South Cove recreation, 1970; UA014.006.010.00022 (Box 10)
  - South Cove, Urban renewal, 1961 -- 1965; UA014.006.010.00023 (Box 10)
  - South Cove, Urban renewal plan, 1962; UA014.006.010.00024 (Box 10)
  - South Cove, Urban renewal plan outline, 1962; UA014.006.010.00025 (Box 10)
  - South Cove Y.M.C.A., 1971; UA014.006.010.00026 (Box 10)
  - Space allocations, 1962 -- 1964; UA014.006.010.00027 (Box 10)
  - Steele, Mary Snyder, Opinions of Selected Patients Concerning Hospital Visiting, 1964; UA014.006.010.00028 (Box 10)
  - Study of existing facilities and new possibilities for floating hospital, 1962; UA014.006.010.00029 (Box 10)
  - Study of mothers' attitudes towards rooming in pediatrics, 1957; UA014.006.010.00030 (Box 10)
  - Summer program, 1963; UA014.006.010.00031 (Box 10)
  - Summer program - patient unit, 1963; UA014.006.010.00032 (Box 10)
  - T.A.C. (The Architects Collective), 1964 -- 1968; UA014.006.010.00033 (Box 10)
  - T-NEMC #7, Hospital evaluation report, 1970 -- 1971; UA014.006.010.00034 (Box 10)
  - T-NEMC, Annual meeting, 1962; UA014.006.010.00035 (Box 10)
  - T-NEMC, Architectural planning proposal, 1964; UA014.006.010.00036 (Box 10)
  - T-NEMC, Development program, 1963 -- 1964; UA014.006.010.00037 (Box 10)
  - T-NEMC, Facilities study, 1962; UA014.006.010.00038 (Box 10)
  - T-NEMC, Facts and figures, photographs, pamphlets, 1965 -- 1970; UA014.006.010.00039 (Box 10)
  - T-NEMC, Grant proposals, elevator study, 1963 -- 1970; UA014.006.010.00040 (Box 10)
  - T-NEMC, Master plan review, 1970; UA014.006.011.00001 (Box 11)
  - T-NEMC, Personnel study, 1964; UA014.006.011.00002 (Box 11)
  - T-NEMC, Planning office library, 1979; UA014.006.011.00003 (Box 11)
  - T-NEMC, Planning office library documents list, 1969 -- 1971; UA014.006.011.00004 (Box 11)
  - T-NEMC, Planning office library documents list, 1969; UA014.006.011.00005 (Box 11)
  - T-NEMC, Planning office library, H.H. Fields, 1969 -- 1971; UA014.006.011.00006 (Box 11)
  - T-NEMC, Property status and unit own., UA014.006.011.00007 (Box 11)
  - T-NEMC, Report on economics of material handling systems, 1968; UA014.006.011.00008 (Box 11)
  - T-NEMC, Report recommendations for materials handling system, 1965; UA014.006.011.00009 (Box 11)
  - Task force, 1970; UA014.006.011.00010 (Box 11)
  - Task force reports, 1967 -- 1969; UA014.006.011.00011 (Box 11)
  - Tour of medical facilities in midwest, 1963; UA014.006.011.00012 (Box 11)
  - Trustees, 1963 -- 1966; UA014.006.011.00013 (Box 11)
  - Tufts medical school - Land, building, space inventory, 1969; UA014.006.011.00014 (Box 11)
  - Tufts teaching - Administrative arr., 1970; UA014.006.011.00015 (Box 11)
  - Tufts University, School of Dental Medicine, experimental dental project, 1966; UA014.006.011.00016 (Box 11)
  - Unit program original, 1963; UA014.006.011.00017 (Box 11)
  - Units, Boston Dispensary, General, 1959; UA014.006.011.00018 (Box 11)
  - Urban renewal property values (South Cove), UA014.006.011.00019 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 7)
  - Urban renewal, U.S. government section 112 credits, 1958 -- 1963; UA014.006.011.00020 (Box 11)
  - Urban renewal, U.S. government, F.H.A. housing section 221d3, 1964 -- 1966; UA014.006.011.00021 (Box 11)
  - Working material, Checker move, 1967; UA014.006.011.00023 (Box 11)
  - Y.M.C.A. use, 1967 -- 1968; UA014.006.011.00024 (Box 11)